<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sagnik Chatterjee</title>
    <link>https://chatsagnik.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sagnik Chatterjee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 21:11:36 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chatsagnik.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://chatsagnik.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 21:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatsagnik.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Ph.D. candidate at the Indraprastha Institute of Information Technology (IIIT-Delhi) advised by Dr. Debajyoti Bera. Previously, I was employed as a software engineer at Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd. in Bangalore.
Research Interests  My primary area of research is Quantum Ensemble Learning which lies at the intersection of quantum computing and learning theory. I am also intertested (and open to collaborations) in many topics across the length and breadth of theoretical CS such as shallow circuit complexity, quantum linear equation solvers, optimization algorithms (both classical and quantum), etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up</title>
      <link>https://chatsagnik.github.io/posts/settingup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:28:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatsagnik.github.io/posts/settingup/</guid>
      <description>  git clone personal_website target_folder_name   hugo new site --force target_folder_name -f yml   cd target_folder_name   git submodule add &amp;lt;url&amp;gt; themes/theme_name --depth=1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chatsagnik.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatsagnik.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>Talks and Resources  Shallow Quantum Circuits This was a talk I gave for Evariste – IIITD’s Theory and Math club.
Abstract: Shallow Quantum Circuits are the quantum analogs of constant depth classical circuits. In 2018, Bravyi et al. showed that there is a relational problem that provides an unconditional separation between SQC’s and constant depth bounded fan-in classical circuits. This started a flurry of research which led to a lot of separation results between SQC’s and stronger classes of classical circuits.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
